<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Full Throttle | Cloud</title><link>http://fullthrottle.cloud/</link><description>Recent content on Full Throttle | Cloud</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Copyright notice</copyright><atom:link href="http://fullthrottle.cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wow that's a lot of ... things in the Cloud Ecosystem</title><link>http://fullthrottle.cloud/cncf-landscape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://fullthrottle.cloud/cncf-landscape/</guid><description>Today, I referred someone to the CNCF landscape site. They were looking for alternatives to a product, and the CNCF Landscape was useful to aggregate a number of those products under a single category. Exploring the CNCF Landscape again today after first discovering it a few weeks ago, I was again overwhelmed at the number of cloud-native products in the ecosystem.
On the one hand I think the landscape is fantastic as a high level organizing filter for cloud products.</description></item><item><title>Sorry, Managing Cloud is Hard</title><link>http://fullthrottle.cloud/cloud-os/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://fullthrottle.cloud/cloud-os/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to figure out how to make it easier to manage cloud environments for about five years now. maybe longer. There are two schools of thought. One - anything at scale is hard, scale is hard, cloud at scale is hard too. theres no shortcuts. I hate this school, its too pessimistic. But it feels right, sadly.
The other school of thought is that we just really havent figured it out yet, maybe theres a tool, technique or method that is so radically simple and easy that it changes whole industries yet.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://fullthrottle.cloud/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://fullthrottle.cloud/about/</guid><description>David Stacy, Cloud Architect and DevOps Specialist</description></item></channel></rss>